Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 11 and District 11 Locals, 1936-1994 UE.4.1.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- District 11, 1.
  - District 11 Ernest DeMaio Outgoing Correspondence, January-March 1952 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Ernest DeMaio to Julius Emspak Regarding Tora Manufacturing and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, January 2, 1952; 1.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Political Action, January 2, 1952; 2.
    - DeMaio to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Smith Act, January 3, 1952; 3.
    - DeMaio to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 4, 1952; 4.
    - DeMaio to Anthony DeMaio Regarding Red-baiting and Political Action, January 8, 1952; 5.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 14, 1952; 6.
    - DeMaio to David Ratner Regading Staff Finances, January 14, 1952; 7.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Wisconsin Steel, United Steelworkers of America Inter-union Rivalry, and Company Union, February 5, 1952; 8.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Finances, February 15, 1952; 9.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Finances and Local 1111, February 15, 1952; 10.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Staff Members, February 15, 1952; 11-12.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Valentino Case, February 18, 1952; 13.
    - DeMaio to Local Union Regarding District Council Meeting, February 22, 1952; 14.
    - DeMaio to Brothers Regarding Red-baiting, United Auto Workers Local 600, and National Negro Labor Council with Raymond Dennis Letter to All Trade Unions, March 11, 1952; 15.
    - DeMaio to All UE Locals Regarding Local 1113 Lock-out, March 20, 1952; 16.
  - District 11 Ernest DeMaio Outgoing Correspondence, April-November 1952 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Ernest DeMaio to District 11 Locals Regarding Local 1113 Lock-out with April 21, 1952, Emil Mueluer Letter, April 22, 1952; 1.
    - DeMaio to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Radio Broadcasts, April 8, 1952; 2.
    - DeMaio to James Matles Regarding Staff Members, May 6, 1952; 3.
    - DeMaio to Stanley Loney Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, May 23, 1952; 4.
    - DeMaio to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances, May 23, 1952; 5.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding International Harvester and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, June 24, 1952; 6.
    - DeMaio to David Ratner Regarding Finances, June 30, 1952; 7.
    - DeMaio to Fitzgerald Regarding Lynn GE and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, July 1, 1952; 8.
    - DeMaio to Anthony DeMaio Regarding Trans World Airlines Cities and Staff Members, July 15, 1952; 9.
    - DeMaio to Ratner Regarding International Harvester Council and Finances, July 24, 1952; 10.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Taxation, August 1, 1952; 11.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Finances and International Harvester Strike, August 21, 1952; 12.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding International Harvester Strike, August 29, 1952; 13.
    - DeMaio to Fitzgerald Regarding International Harvester Strike, August 29, 1952; 14.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Quad Cities, August 29, 1952; 15.
    - DeMaio to Sir Regarding House Un-American Activities Committee, September 3, 1952; 16.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Sentner Case, September 30, 1952; 17.
    - DeMaio to Pietro Lucchi Regarding International Harvester Strike, African-Americans, and UAW Inter-union Rivalry, October 24, 1952; 18.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding International Harvester Strike, October 24, 1952; 19.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding International Harvester Strike, October 30, 1952; 20.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding International Harvester Strike and Minneapolis-Moline Contracts, November 20, 1952; 21.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding International Harvester Strike, November 20, 1952; 22.
  - District 11 Ernest DeMaio Outgoing Correspondence, December 1952-September 1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Ernest DeMaio to James Matles Regarding International Harvester Strike, December 1, 1952; 1.
    - DeMaio to Julius Emspak Regarding Finances and Locals 1140 and 1145, January 13, 1953; 2.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding International Harvester Strike, January 16, 1953; 3.
    - DeMaio to Meyers and Rothstein Regarding Ward Case, January 16, 1953; 4.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Ward Case and International Harvester Strike, January 16, 1953; 5.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Finances, January 23, 1953; 6.
    - DeMaio to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 1119 Disbanding, January 30, 1953; 7.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Finances, Janaury 23, 1953; 8.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Local 1145 and Inter-union Rivalry with IUE and Teamsters, February 27, 1953; 9.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Local 1153 and Finances, February 27, 1953; 10.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Finances, March 5, 1953; 11.
    - DeMaio to Emspak Regarding Women, March 24, 1953; 12.
    - DeMaio to Edward Matthews Regarding Local 111, March 30, 1953; 13.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Local 1114 Strike at Honeywell in Minneapolis, April 9, 1953; 14.
    - DeMaio to Fitzgerald Regarding African-Americans and Women, May 18, 1953; 15.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Staff Members, June 22, 1953; 16.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, July 8, 1953; 17.
    - DeMaio to David Ratner Regarding Finances, September 30, 1953; 18.
  - District 11 Ernest DeMaio Outgoing Correspondence, October 1953-June 1955 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Ernest DeMaio to James Matles Regarding Local 1114 Strike at Brad Foote and American Gear and Inter-union Rivalry with the United Steelworkers and Teamsters, October 15, 1953; 1.
    - DeMaio to David Ratner Regarding Locals 107F and 108F and Per Capita, October 20, 1953; 2.
    - DeMaio to Matthew Bednarz Regarding Finances and Locals 101F and 141F, October 26, 1953; 3.
    - DeMaio to Janet Barish Regarding Finances, November 10, 1953; 4.
    - DeMaio to Robert Logsdon Regarding Finances, December 29, 1953; 5.
    - DeMaio to Fred Saniat Regarding Local 1114 and Miehle Press Separate Charter, December 29, 1953; 6.
    - DeMaio to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Local 107 and Inter-union Rivalry, January 15, 1954; 7.
    - DeMaio to Don Harris Regarding National Dairy Producers Conference, January 26, 1954; 8.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Staff Members, August 23, 1954; 9.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Local 1150, September 1, 1954; 10.
    - DeMaio to Julius Emspak Regarding UE News, September 2, 1954; 11.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Staff Members, September 14, 1954; 12.
    - DeMaio to District 11 Locals Regarding Square D Strike and United Auto Workers, September 15, 1954; 13.
    - DeMaio to Ratner Regarding Staff Finances, September 20, 1954; 14.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, September 22, 1954; 15.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Staff Members, December 4, 1954; 16.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Staff Finances, December 15, 1954; 17.
    - DeMaio to Matles Regarding Local 1114, December 27, 1954; 18.
    - DeMaio to Fitzgerald Regarding Labor Unity, May 4, 1955; 19.
    - DeMaio to Joe Falis Regarding Local 207 Strike at Lander, June 13, 1955; 20.
  - District 11 Ernest DeMaio Outgoing Correspondence, September-December 1955 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Ernest DeMaio to Julius Emspak Regarding District Council Meeting, September 28, 1955; 1.
    - DeMaio to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Labor Unity Factionalism, October 24, 1955; 2.
    - DeMaio to District 11 Locals Regarding Westinghouse Strike, October 26, 1955; 3.
    - DeMaio to Brothers Regarding Westinghouse Strike, December 30, 1955; 4.
    - DeMaio to Fitzgerald Regarding Midwest Visit, December 30, 1955; 5.
  - District 11 President Ernest DeMaio District 11 Correspondence, 1956-1961 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - District 11 President Ernest DeMaio District 11 Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - District 11 President Ernest DeMaio District 11 Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - District 11 Buford Eastman Incoming Correspondence, 1939-1942 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - James Carey to Buford Eastman Regarding Minneapolis Visit, December 18, 1939; 1.
    - Carey to Eastman Regarding Citizens Council for National Defense, September 25, 1940; 2.
    - Carey to Eastman Regarding Factionalism, November 25, 1940; 3.
    - Carey to Eastman Regarding Factionalism, December 5, 1940; 4.
    - Julius Emspak to Eastman Regarding Per Capita, Minneapolis, and the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, July 11, 1941; 5.
    - Emspak to Eastman Regarding Milwaukee Organization, February 7, 1941; 6.
    - Emspak to Eastman Regarding Local 1150 Organization, May 8, 1941; 7.
    - Emspak to Eastman Regarding Per Capita, November 7, 1941; 8.
    - Emspak to Eastman Regarding Supplies, January 22, 1942; 9.
    - Emspak to Eastman Regarding Local 1113 and Factionalism, March 11, 1942; 10.
    - Emspak to Eastman Regarding Districts 8 and 11, May 13, 1942; 11.
    - Albert Fitzgerald to Eastman Regarding Military Service, February 5, 1942; 12.
  - District 11 Buford Eastman Incoming Correspondence, 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - James Matles to Buford Eastman Regarding Staff Members and the CIO Convention, November 28, 1938; 1.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members, November 29, 1938; 2.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Chicago Organization, December 6, 1938; 3.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Factionalism, April 27, 1939; 4.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Warwick Radio Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 20, 1939; 5.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members and Milwaukee, October 2, 1939; 6.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Warwick Radio Organization and Locals 1109 and 1121 with September 25, 1939 George Hayden Letter to James Carey and September 26, 1939, Victoria Berek Letter to Carey, October 2, 1939; 7.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, October 3, 1939; 8.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members, November 8, 1939; 9.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, January 9, 1940; 10.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, January 18, 1940; 11.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding UE News, February 9, 1940; 12.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding the General Executive Board and Minnesota Congress of Industrial Organizations, August 2, 1950; 13.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Per Capita and Honeywell Organization, September 27, 1940; 14.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members and Milwaukee, January 20, 1941; 15.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Chicago Organization and Staff Members, February 4, 1941; 16.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members, February 7, 1941; 17.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members, May 8, 1941; 18.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Garage Dealers Strike, May 15, 1941; 19.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Garage Workers Strike and Minneapolis Honeywell, May 26, 1941; 20.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Minneapolis Visit, July 7, 1941; 21.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Honeywell Organization, July 22, 1941; 22.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Honeywell Organization, August 5, 1941; 23.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Honeywell Organization, August 6, 1941; 24.
  - District 11 Buford Eastman Incoming Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - James Matles to Buford Eastman Regarding Staff Members, August 26, 1941; 1.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Mitchell Battery Organization, September 10, 1941; 2.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Twentieth Century Brass and Electric Machine Negotiations, September 12, 1941; 3.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Honeywell Organization, September 22, 1941; 4.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Minneapolis Visit, Battery Shops Elections, and Electric Machinery Strike, October 2, 1941; 5.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members and Chicago, October 23, 1941; 6.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Jordan Electric and Grant Battery Organization, October 31, 1941; 7.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members and Conscription, November 12, 1941; 8.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding National Battery Organization and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, November 12, 1941; 9.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Honeywell Organization, November 25, 1941; 10.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members, November 25, 1941; 11.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members, December 4, 1941; 12.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Finances and Locals 11 and 5, December 5, 1941; 13.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members, January 13, 1942; 14.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Honeywell Organization, January 19, 1942; 15.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Owatanna Organization, January 19, 1942; 16.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Foundry Workers and Molders Inter-union Rivalry, January 22, 1942; 17.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Seniority and General Motors, February 19, 1942; 18.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Local 1145 and Finances, February 25, 1942; 19.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding the FBI, March 9, 1942; 20.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Vacations, March 12, 1942; 21.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Conscription, April 9, 1942; 22.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Finances and Local 1145, April 13, 1942; 23.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Staff Members, April 24, 1942; 24.
    - Matles to Eastman Regarding Northwestern Auto Parts Organization, May 7, 1942; 25.
    - William Sentner to Eastman Regarding Minneapolis Moline Organization, February 8, 1942; 26.
    - Unsigned Letter to Eastman Regarding Honeywell Military Organization, July 8, 1942; 27.
    - Unsigned Letter to Eastman Regarding Factionalism, January 11, 1943; 28.
  - District 11 Buford Eastman Outgoing Correspondence, November 1938-July 1941 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Buford Eastman to James Matles Regarding Pittsburgh Visit, November 1, 1938; 1.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Moline Negotiations, November 23, 1938; 2.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Hudson Strike, January 26, 1939; 3.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Factionalism and Local 1140, April 17, 1939; 4.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Factionalism, Minneapolis, and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, April 20, 1939; 5.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding District Officers and Factionalism, September 29, 1939; 6.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Factionalism, October 5, 1939; 7.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Factionalism, January 15, 1940; 8.
    - Eastman to Julius Emspak Regarding Minneapolis Honeywell Organization, March 26, 1940; 9.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Minneapolis Honeywell Organization, July 10, 1940; 10.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Minnesota Congress of Industrial Organizations, July 26, 1940; 11.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding 1940 UE Convention and Factionalism, August 21, 1940; 12.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Factionalism and Organization, September 18, 1940; 13.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Per Capita and Milwaukee Organization, January 13, 1941; 14.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Garage Workers Strike, April 30, 1941; 15.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Minneapolis Honeywell Organization, May 9, 1941; 16.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Garage Workers Contract and Honeywell Organization, May 19, 1941; 17.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Wausau Strike, Honeywell Organization, and Independent Garages Strike, June 30, 1941; 18.
    - Eastman to Emspak Regarding Wages, Battery Industry, and Per Capita, July 3, 1941; 19.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Local 1146, Per Capita, Honeywell Organization, and Independent Garages Strike, July 18, 1941; 20.
    - Eastman to Emspak Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, Battery Industry Wages, and Local 1111, July 23, 1941; 21.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry and Honeywell Organization with Leaflet and Newspaper Clipping, July 25, 1941; 22.
  - District 11 Buford Eastman Outgoing Correspondence, August 1941-January 1942 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Buford Eastman to James Matles Regarding Battery Workers and Honeywell Organization, August 8, 1941; 1.
    - Eastman to Julius Emspak Regarding Honeywell Organization and Inter-union Rivalry, August 13, 1941; 2.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Honeywell Organization and Strikes, September 10, 1941; 3.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Honeywell Organization and National Labor Relations Board, September 16, 1941; 4.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Honeywell Organization, Local 1139, Molders Inter-union Rivalry, Organization, and Strikes, September 30, 1941; 5.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Hill Manufacturing Contract, Mitchell Battery Organization, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, and Local 1139, October 6, 1941; 6.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Local 1139, Foundry Workers Inter-union Rivalry with Molders and Factionalism, October 15, 1941; 7.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Battery Workers Negotiations, Honeywell Organization, and Factionalism, October 20, 1941; 8.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Honeywell Organization and Staff Members, October 21, 1941; 9.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Battery Industry Organization, October 24, 1941; 10.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Battery Shops Contract and Moline Organization, October 29, 1941; 11.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding International Harvester Organization, Inter-union Rivalry, and Staff Members, November 26, 1941; 12.
    - Eastman to Albert Fitzgerald Regarding District Council Meeting, November 26, 1941; 13.
    - Eastman to Emspak Regarding Local 1145, Finances, Battery Shops Wages, and Unemployment, December 5, 1941; 14.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding National Battery, IBEW Inter-union Rivalry, and Staff Members, December 10, 1941; 15.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Women, December 23, 1941; 16.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Staff Members and Owatanna Organization, January 6, 1942; 17.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Honeywell Organization, January 7, 1942; 18.
    - Eastman to Emspak Regarding Local 1138 and Factionalism, January 9, 1942; 19.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Seniority with Certificate, January 14, 1942; 20.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 23, 1942; 21.
    - Eastman to Fitzgerald Regarding Congress of Industrial Organizations Victory Conference, January 27, 1942; 22.
  - District 11 Buford Eastman Outgoing Correspondence, February-December 1942 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Buford Eastman to James Matles Regarding Staff Members and Minnesota Congress of Industrial Organizations, February 4, 1942; 1.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Negotiations, February 20, 1942; 2.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Vacations and Local 1145, February 27, 1942; 3.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding the FBI, March 2, 1942; 4.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Negotiations and Contracts, March 5, 1942; 5.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Contracts, March 14, 1942; 6.
    - Eastman to Julius Emspak Regarding Productivity Councils and Organization, March 13, 1942; 7.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Kaidong Contract and Local 1140, March 30, 1942; 8.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Army, April 1, 1942; 9.
    - Eastman to Emspak Regarding District 8 and Moline, May 5, 1942; 10.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Pioneer Engineering Contract, May 7, 1942; 11.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Northwestern Auto Parks Organization, May 13, 1942; 12.
    - Eastman to Matles Regarding Local 1121 and General Motors Service Organization, May 19, 1942; 13.
    - Eastman to Emspak Regarding Military, June 28, 1942; 14.
    - Eastman to Emspak Regarding Military and Factionalism, December 20, 1942; 15.
  - District 11 Frank Rosen Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - District 11 General Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1950 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - James Carey to Larry Kimmel Regarding King Colonial Negotiations and Grunow Strike, May 27, 1936; 1.
    - Carey to Kimmel Regarding General Executive Board Meeting, December 2, 1936; 2.
    - Carey to Kimmel Regarding General Executive Board Meeting, December 7, 1936; 3.
    - Carey to Kimmel Regarding Organization and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, January 19, 1937; 4.
    - Carey to Kimmel Regarding Organization and Staff Members, January 22, 1937; 5.
    - Carey to Kimmel Regarding Organization, March 18, 1937; 6.
    - Carey to Kimmel Regarding Organization, April 2, 1937; 7.
    - Carey to Kimmel, November 29, 1938; 8.
    - Carey to Kimmel, June 6, 1939; 9.
    - Julius Emspak to Kimmel Regarding RCA Strike, July 7, 1936; 10.
    - Emspak to Kimmel Regarding American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, August 14, 1936; 11.
    - Emspak to Kimmel Regarding District Council, March 25, 1937; 12.
    - Emspak to Kimmel Regarding Minneapolis Organization, December 18, 1937; 13.
    - Emspak to Harry Wold Regarding Organization, July 16, 1941; 14.
    - Emspak to Wold Regarding Civil Service, July 17, 1941; 15.
    - Emspak to Harley Wright Regarding District 11 Officers, June 25, 1942; 16.
    - Emspak to General Executive Board Members Regarding Dues and Veterans, May 31, 1945; 17.
    - Emspak to R. Bergstrom Regarding Finances, April 27, 1949; 18.
    - Emspak to Wayne Smith Regarding Finances, April 13, 1950; 19.
    - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding District 11 Officers, July 8, 1942; 20.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Womens' Conference, March 20, 1945; 21.
  - District 11 General Incoming Correspondence, 1937-1955 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - James Matles Regarding Organization, July 9, 1937; 1.
    - Matles Regarding Minneapolis and American Federation of Labor Inter-union Rivalry, October 8, 1937; 2.
    - Matles to Larry Kimmel Regarding Staff Members, Organization, District Constitution, and Minnesota, January 19, 1938; 3.
    - Matles to Kimmel Regarding Staff Members, February 2, 1938; 4.
    - Matles to Albert Scheluis Regarding Westinghouse and Boycotts, March 2, 1938; 5.
    - Matles to Kimmel Regarding Finances, April 2, 1938; 6.
    - Matles to Kimmel Regarding Factionalism and Finances, April 11, 1938; 7.
    - Matles to Kimmel Regarding Factionalism and Staff Members, April 19, 1938; 8.
    - Matles to Kimmel Regarding ABC Washing and District 8, May 11, 1938; 9.
    - Matles to Kimmel Regarding Local 1138 Organization, July 5, 1938; 10.
    - Matles to Kimmel Regarding Midwest Trip, July 27, 1938; 11.
    - Matles to Harley Wright Regarding Staff Members, September 22, 1942; 12.
    - Matles to Robert Wishart Regarding Strikes, January 8, 1946; 13.
    - Matles to Wishart Regarding Staff Members, January 9, 1946; 14.
    - Matles to Wishart Regarding Westinghouse and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 31, 1946; 15.
    - Matles to Forrest Emerson Regarding UE News, July 27, 1950; 16.
    - Matles to Wilham Burch Regarding International Harvester and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, July 8, 1955; 17.
    - William Sentner Regarding International Harvester and UAW Inter-union Rivalry with Leaflet, October 18, 1950; 18.
    - Al Stonkus to Earl McGrew Regarding Steelworkers Organizing Committee Inter-union Rivalry, Factionalism, and Tuthill Pump, September 27, 1939; 19.
  - District 11 General Outgoing Correspondence, 1936-1950 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Frat Emerson to Beecher Regarding "F" Locals, April 4, 1950; 1.
    - Emerson to James Matles Regarding Women's Auxliaries with Charter and Constitution Excerpt, June 12, 1950; 2.
    - Emerson to Matles, June 26, 1950; 3.
    - Emerson to Matles Regarding Red-baiting, Factionalism, and United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, October 25, 1950; 4.